Yeah, I feel pretty good about myseIf.
Do you think we can outrun him?
(Sheldon:)I don't need to outrun him.
I just need to outrun you.
(Bernadette:)I don't feel good about this.
Well, then, sit in the car
and keep it running.
(Amy:)You were right. A whole new load.
(Penny:)Come on, yoga top.
Momma needs a new yoga top.
(Amy:)Check it out, Bernadette.
Suede boots. Your size.
(Bernadette:)God, they're cute.
Oh, why did they have to be cute?
(Penny:)Wait, wait, wait, guys. Just hang on.
What is it? The fuzz?
Oh, look at us. What are we doing?
I was following you
to a life of crime...
(Amy:)...looking forward
to the day we might be cell mates.
(Amy:)I don't know about Bernadette.
No, this is wrong.
Let's put everything back. Come on.
(Leonard:)Here.
(Bernadette(taking boots and running):)It's okay, I serve soup to poor people.